<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Antoine André on Home</title><link>https://antoineandre.github.io/contributors/antoine-andr%C3%A9/</link><description>Recent content in Antoine André on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:16:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://antoineandre.github.io/contributors/antoine-andr%C3%A9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>List of presentations</title><link>https://antoineandre.github.io/presentations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:16:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://antoineandre.github.io/presentations/</guid><description>France #
Japan #</description></item><item><title>List of Publications, Talks, Softwares &amp; Datasets</title><link>https://antoineandre.github.io/publi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:16:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://antoineandre.github.io/publi/</guid><description>Peer-Reviewed Journals #
First Author
André, A. N., Lehmann, O., Govilas, J., Laurent, G. J., Saadana, H., Sandoz, P., Gauthier, V., Lefèvre, A., Bolopion, A., Agnus, J., Placet, V. &amp;amp; Clévy, C. (2022). Automating Robotic Micro-Assembly of Fluidic Chips and Single Fiber Compression Tests Based-on $ XY\Theta $ Visual Measurement With High-Precision Fiducial Markers. IEEE Transactions on Automation Science and Engineering.
André, A. N., Sandoz, P., Jacquot, M., &amp;amp; Laurent, G.</description></item><item><title>Research interests, associates and projects</title><link>https://antoineandre.github.io/research/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 11:16:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://antoineandre.github.io/research/</guid><description>Research interests #
Computer vision for robotics Omnidirectional cameras High resolution pose estimation Supervision #
Thomas Duvinage (engineer&amp;rsquo;s degree, UTBM, autumn 2023), encapsulate spherical Visual Servoing in a multi-objective control framework Matthieu Quaccia (engineer&amp;rsquo;s degree, INSA Toulouse, spring 2023, co-supervision), implementation of feature maps for Direct Visual Servoing Quentin Milot (engineer&amp;rsquo;s degree, INSA Rennes, spring 2022, co-supervision), Adaptation for omnidirectional cameras of a SLAM (Simultaneous Localization and Mapping) algorithm Valériia Leush (engineer&amp;rsquo;s degree, ENSMM, spring 2021), Software development of a python tool, based on the Vernier library, to generate and measure periodic pattern poses Projects participation #
DVS-Straight (AIST-ITH funding, 2021-2024), Direct Visual Servoing with optimal robot trajectories Holonet (ISITE BFC funding, 2020-2023), Toward extended visual control capabilities using digital holography Nano6D (regional funding, 2018-2021), 3D metrology at nanoscale</description></item></channel></rss>